futurespros.com 2013-05-31

# Privacy Policy

Fusion Media Limited. (Hereinafter "Investing.com" or "the Company" or "Fusion Media Ltd." or "Fusion Media" or "we") is the owner of this website Investing.com ("The website") Fusion Media is committed to protecting your privacy. This "Privacy Policy" describes how we collect, store and use information on individuals that use this Web Site.

FUSION MEDIA Privacy Pledge

The term "personal data" as used in this Policy refers to information such as your name, e-mail address or mailing address, or any data that can be used to identify you. We ensure that our staff and those acting on our behalf obtain, use and disclose personal information lawfully and correctly. 

Automatically Collected Information - When you use or visit our Website, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. Our server logs may include information such as, your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser language, web pages you visit before or after visiting our Website, URL’s, platform type, clicks number, domain names, landing pages, viewed pages and the order of those pages and time spent on pages. 

“Cookies” - When visiting or using our Website, we may send one or more “cookies”. “Cookies” are small bits of code, usually stored on a user's computer hard drive, which enable a Website to "personalize" itself for each user. 

Web Beacons - We may use a software technology called “clear gifs” (also known as Web Beacons). Web Beacons are small pieces of code placed on a web page to monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page. For example, web beacons can be used to count the users who visit a web page or to deliver a “cookie” to the browser of a visitor viewing that page. 

Sharing Information with Our Affiliates

We may share personal information described above with our affiliates for business purposes, such as informing customers about new products and services, and as permitted by applicable law. Our affiliates may include companies controlled or owned by us. The information we share with affiliates may include any of the information types described above. Our affiliates maintain the privacy of your information to the same extent Fusion Media does in accordance with this Policy.

Sharing Information with Third Parties

Fusion Media does not disclose your personal information to third parties, except as described in this Policy. Third party disclosures may include sharing such information with non-affiliated. Non-affiliated companies that assist Fusion Media in providing services to you are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information to the extent they receive it and to use your personal information only in the course of providing such services and only for the purposes that Fusion Media dictates. Fusion Media reserve the right to sell such information to third parties who might be interested in offering its services to Fusion Media’s Customers to which Fusion Media finds appropriate to offer its customer base. Such third parties may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to compile information about your browser’s or device’s visits and usage patterns, measure the effectiveness and accuracy of their content and/or advertisements and to personalize the content and/or advertisements targeted to you. Fusion Media may also disclose your personal information to third parties to fulfill your instructions or pursuant to your express consent. However, please note that if a third party, asks us to show content and/or advertisement to a certain audience segment and you respond to that, that third party may conclude that you fit the characteristics of such audience. This third party may also use information regarding your use of the Website, such as the number of times you viewed specific content and/or an advertisement, to determine which content and/or advertisements to deliver to you. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to these third parties, and we cannot control their activities.

Right of information

The Company informs you that the collection and processing of personal data is aimed at providing you with services offered by this website and to send you commercial information on products or services you may be interested in. The Company will store this data as long as it is reasonably necessary to attain the mentioned purposes and in accordance with any applicable legal or ethical requirement.

Consent to use information

By using this Web Site, or providing information to us in other formats, you consent to the collection and use of this information by The Company.

Mandatory and optional information

In order to use our services, users may be asked to fill in a form, which requires providing certain personal information to The Company. Unless otherwise provided in those fields expressly marked with an asterisk , answers to our questions on personal data are not mandatory. Not providing the information required in such optional fields shall not represent any decrease of the services and information that we may provide. However, failure to complete those compulsory fields or providing incorrect personal data shall prevent us from providing the requested information or services.

Rights of access, rectification, cancellation and objection

The Company informs you of the possibility of exercising your rights to access, rectify, cancel and object to the processing of your personal data simply by making a written request to Fusion Media.com using our contact us page. Your requests will be dealt with in a prompt and proper manner.

Security and confidentiality

The Company guarantees that your personal data will be treated with the strictest confidentiality, and that the server in which these data will be stored and dealt with has implemented the necessary industry-standard security measures to prevent accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access to the above-mentioned data. However, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of your information, which might be accessed, disclosed, modified, or destroyed, and it should be emphasized that you do so at your own risk.

Links to other websites

This Privacy Policy applies only to this Web Site, excluding third party websites, as we may provide links to other websites which we believe may be of interest to our visitors. We aim at ensuring that such websites are of the highest standard. However, due to the nature of the World Wide Web, we cannot guarantee the standards of every linked website or be responsible for their content.

Assignment and opt-out

We may transfer and/or assign your information, without any notice, and without a need to receive your consent, to any third party as a result of change of control, consolidation, merger, acquisition or reorganization. 

If you would like to opt out of DoubleClick's use of cookies you can do so by visiting the [DoubleClick opt-out page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb#display_optout) or the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

Updates to this policy

Should THE COMPANY amend this Privacy Policy in order to adapt it to new legal requirements, we will immediately post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we gather, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
